# VINCCI TSUI

## FRONT END DEVELOPER

www.vinccitsui.me

#### CONTACT

Email: vinccimantsui@gmail.com

Cell: +16472864800 GitHub: @<u>vt1022</u>

LinkedIn: /vinccimantsui

#### **ABOUT**

I am a web developer with design experience. I am currently fluent in React, JavaScript, jQuery, HTML, CSS and Sass. I find the middle ground of functionality, aesthetics, and user experience. As a believer in universal design, I pay attention to UX and accessibility as I code.

#### SKILLS

React
JavaScript
TypeScript
jQuery
AJAX, AXIOS (REST Api)
Firebase
CSS, SASS
HTML
Git, GitHub
Visual Studio Code
Responsive Design
Accessible Design
Adobe Photoshop
Adobe Illustrator

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### UI Engineer | Coates Group | 2021 - present

- Primarily worked with React, Redux, Sass, JavaScript. Occasionally used TypeScript
- Worked with design team to prototype and deliver time-sensitive projects for McDonald's Canada
- Brought new features to life from ideation to final product
- Trained new team members on JavaScript and CSS best practices and common debugging processes

### Junior Web Developer | Coates Group | 2020 - 2021

- Worked extensively with Sass and React to map out dynamic content
- Used CSS to style captivating menu boards for McDonald's Canada
- Fetched data from internal database to be displayed on the menus
- Solved compatibility issues caused by required support of older browser versions
- Worked closely with QA, CMS, and Design team in an agile environment

#### Freelance | Che Patisserie | www.chepatisserie.com | 2021

- e-Commerce website designed and developed for small bakery selling weekly products
- Used mobile-first best practices to align with the usage patterns of majority end-users
- Integrated to pull data from Google Sheets to simplify content updates by non-technical client
- Leveraged Email|S to send automated confirmation/invoice emails to customers
- Integrated Discord webhooks to send notifications to business when an order is complete

#### **PROJECTS**

# PokeMatch| jQuery, Sass | <u>LINK</u>

- A game to match pairs of face down Pokemon cards
- Flexbox and media queries for responsive design
- Tabindex property to ensure accessibility
- Discovered the beauty of using BEM with Sass

#### **EDUCATION**

Web Dev Immersive. Juno College (HackerYou). 2020
Accelerated JavaScript and Web Dev. Juno College (HackerYou). 2019
Packaging Design. Humber College. 2012 - 2015
Industrial Design. Ontario College of Arts and Design. 2008 - 2010